<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-03-03T22:58:20-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">English 101</title><subtitle>I put my academic work here</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Writing assignment # 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/11/28/paper-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Writing assignment # 3" /><published>2022-11-28T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2022-11-28T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/11/28/paper-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/11/28/paper-3.html">&lt;p&gt;Jiantao Li&lt;br /&gt;
Dr. Tagnani&lt;br /&gt;
ENGL 101&lt;br /&gt;
November 28, 2022&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Research Argument: &lt;br /&gt;The impact of the corporatization of higher education is doing more harm than good&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the changes of the times, the increase in population, and the advancement of science and technology, the importance of receiving education has been paid more and more attention, and it is not difficult to find that in the current education system, there are many non-local students, which we call international students who study in different countries in search of a better education. This phenomenon is particularly evident in higher education. In recent years, more universities have begun recruiting international students, and the emergence of international students has brought many advantages to schools, such as high tuition fees, making universities more internationalized and diversified. In order to adapt to this trend of internationalization and diversification, more and more universities are becoming corporate. For example, employ more flexible adjunct professors instead of full-time professors, and recruit more administrative staff instead of professors. However, this raises a controversial question of the pros and cons of corporatization in higher education institutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think corporatization in higher education is doing more harm than good. It is reasonable for universities to diversify and internationalize because they need more students to bring benefits, and students just need to seek better education, which is a win-win situation for both schools and students. But the emergence of corporatization is not all good for schools, professors, and students, and even the harm outweighs the good. In this regard,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, although there is no doubt that corporatization provides students with more opportunities, I think the impact of university corporatization on students is negative, especially financially.
According to the article “Corporatizing Higher Education” (Lerner) mentioned the impact of university corporatization, “The simultaneous increase in the use of contingent faculty; the rise in tuition; the dramatic decrease in federal and state aid to universities and state colleges and the outsourcing of campus bookstores, food services, and custodial work.” So, we know that the corporatization of universities involves rising tuition fees, increasing the use of temporary teachers, etc. Thus, the first disadvantage of the corporatization of higher education appears, that, for students, high tuition fees are stressful. According to the data provided by the article “The Corporatization of Higher Education” (Mills), “At elite schools, 74 percent of the student body come from the top quarter of the socioeconomic scale, while just 3 percent come from the bottom quarter.” Therefore, I think that due to the emergence of the corporatization of higher education, the increase in tuition fees has created financial pressure on many students, because many students’ families cannot afford high tuition fees, which prevents them from going to good schools. Students can go to relatively average schools with lower tuition fees, but before the tuition fees become higher (or we can say before the emergence of corporatization), they can go to better schools, and corporatization has greatly reduced this possibility. It also means that many gifted students will not be able to get into elite schools because they cannot afford the high tuition fees. What’s more, most of the students are very ordinary and have no family background. In this regard, I think that in addition to elite schools, the tuition fees of many schools are also ridiculously high. I am an international student, so my tuition fees will be much more expensive than local students, and because of the global economic problems in recent years, the high tuition fees and exchange rates have put my family under heavy pressure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, the impact of corporatization is not only the pressure on tuition fees, the cost of special courses such as extracurricular tutoring is also beyond the reach of ordinary families. According to the “star system” mentioned in the article “Corporatizing Higher Education”, “Research universities and private institutions, always intent on improving their ranking and national stature, tend to select prospective ‘ stars” in their job searches.” This would make both the school and the student seek “market value”. Combined with the information provided in the article “The Corporatization of Higher Education”, “But an altogether different process is going on, one that has saddled us with a higher-education model that is both expensive to run and difficult to reform as a result of its focus on status, its view of students as customers” We can understand that the purpose of the corporatization of universities is to attract students, and the school can gain benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thence, as an extension and derivative of university corporatization, the “star system“ has increased the status of the school and attracted many students at the same time. Therefore, good students will choose better educational institutions, and as I mentioned above, these good educational institutions often charge higher tuition fees. At the same time, good educational institutions seek out and attract good students. Because of this, the value of a student’s SAT, GPA, and test results are highly valued to improve a school’s ranking and status. For this reason, many students choose to participate in training and counseling so that they can be admitted to good schools. However, this has led to wealthy families having a better chance of being admitted to schools because they can afford to tutor, while middle-class families and disadvantaged groups are not admitted to schools that care about market value because they cannot afford to tutor. Also, as the article “Corporatizing Higher Education” said, “Thus, the corporatization of institutions has reinforced an already existing disparity in access to higher education between the wealthy, the middle class, and the less privileged.”, because extracurricular fees harbor Tutor-led to a widening gap between rich and poor students in schools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, I think the corporatization of higher education is negative for students, especially when it comes to fees. Wealthy families have a lot of extra expenses because of the trend of college corporatization, such as higher tuition fees and fees for extracurriculars and special courses. And students from the middle class and disadvantaged groups cannot receive a better education because they cannot pay high tuition fees and cannot be noticed by the “star system” because they cannot pay for extracurricular tutoring courses. What’s more, it is likely to burden many families with loans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, I don’t think the corporatization of universities is good for adjunct professors at all. 
as I mentioned in the first paragraph, the article “Corporatizing Higher Education”  mentioned the impact of university corporatization, “The simultaneous increase in the use of contingent faculty; the rise in tuition; the dramatic decrease in federal and state aid to universities and state colleges and the outsourcing of campus bookstores, food services, and custodial work.“ For professors, the situation they face is an increase in the number of times they are used. 
The corporatization of universities means that they need to save as much cost as possible, so corporatized universities tend to recruit more part-time professors, and reduce costs, in other words, to squeeze the labor force of part-time professors.&lt;br /&gt;
“According to Department of Education post-secondary school data for fall 2013, 64 percent of faculty at public four-year research institutions are contingent compared with 80 percent at public two-year colleges and 100 percent at for-profit colleges”. According to data provided by this article “Contingent Faculty of the World Unite! Organizing to Resist the Corporation of Higher Education” (Daniel), we can clearly realize that in recent years, most of the school’s professors are part-time professors. However, the article also states that “In 1975, there were 623,000 faculty in the United States (excluding graduate students), 29 percent of them tenured, and another 16 percent on the tenure track. In 2011, there were just under 1.5 million faculty (excluding graduate students), just over 16.7 percent of them tenured, and 7.4 percent on track for tenure, according to a 2013 AAUP report.” While the total number of professors increased by nearly 1 million from 1975 to 2013, only 16.7% of professors were tenure-tracked, up from just 0.7% in 1975. This means that it is now increasingly difficult for professors to secure tenure or adequate security. Therefore, the corporatization of universities has directly led to an increase in the number of part-time professors, while the wages and benefits have decreased, and sufficient guarantees cannot be obtained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only that, but the salary of adjunct professors also has a large gap with that of full-time professors. Combined with the “star system” mentioned above, “Corporatizing Higher Education” provides a clear table that proves the gap between the highest salary of professors (star professors in the star system) and the lowest salary (adjunct professors). The table shows that at private schools, the highest salary for professors ranged from $86,000 in 1985 to $193,000 in 2006. In contrast, the minimum wage only ranges from $11,000 to $27,000. Moreover, the gap in public schools is even greater. has risen from nearly $70,000 to nearly $240,000, but the minimum wage has risen from $15,000 to $21,000. Even from 1989 to 2000, the minimum wage still went down. The article also pointed out, “The actuality is even worse—part-time faculty get paid as low as $1500 per semester course, without health and retirement benefits, and frequently they work without permanent offices. They are hired semester to semester and have no job guarantee.” Combining these data, it is not difficult to see that due to the gradual advancement of corporatization, the lower the status of adjunct professors, the less secure they are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To sum up, as mentioned in the article “The Corporatization of Higher Education” the problems faced by adjunct professors are not only the workload and remuneration, but they are also helpless when it comes to students. “Casual teachers cannot help students with advising, career planning, or attention to personal learning issues. Casual teachers often have a greater workload than regular teachers; they teach Classes that are larger and most’ lectures are frequent. Under such working conditions, even those highly qualified and motivated teachers cannot do their job as well as the teaching staff get decent salaried jobs. “ Due to the emergence and prevalence of corporatization, universities began to hire more adjunct professors to reduce costs. This also means that although the employment rate of adjunct professors has increased, their remuneration has not increased or even decreased due to the increase in the number of part-time professors. For example, the salary is much lower than that of normal professors, the chances of obtaining tenured teaching positions are reduced, the workload is increased, and there are no retirement benefits and a series of guarantees. These are of no benefit to the adjunct professors whose total number has risen considerably.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third, unlike part-time professors, although the salary of full-time professors has been increased, it has also been greatly affected by the emergence of corporatization. As universities hire adjunct professors in large numbers, full-time professors are also at risk of layoffs. Due to corporatization, the means for universities to reduce costs is not only to hire low-paid part-time professors but also to lay off some full-time professors to reduce wages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As mentioned in the article “Faculty Activism and the Corporatization of the University” (Bose), corporatization actually changed the working conditions of professors. “Within the university, corporatization has radically altered the conditions of work for the professorate, in some cases eliminating programs or units in their academic specialties, ratcheting up standards of productivity, and increasing faculty’s general workload in response to the downsizing of academic personnel.” Corporatization not only increases the workload of the professors mentioned above but also lays off the school’s professors. This also means that corporatization has led to the insecurity of both full-time and part-time professors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides, the power of full-time and tenured professors has also been reduced due to the corporatization of universities. According to the idea mentioned in the article “Corporatizing Higher Education”, because professors need to assign and transfer power to more administrative staff. “The impact on governance in academic institutions will be more serious. It is tenured professors who take most responsibility for committee work and participation in the governance of the institutions.” As the temp workforce increases, the number of full-time and tenured professors decreases, and the less influential they become. At the same time, their powers were handed over to executives who had been augmented by corporatization. Not all good for full-time professors. Because they will face the risk of layoffs and the transfer of power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the reason why I think corporatization does more harm than good to higher education is that for students, it raises tuition fees and increases the cost of extracurricular tutoring and special courses, which ordinary families cannot afford, and it also made the class gap within the university even wider. At the same time, corporatization has made part-time professors face the impact of increased workload and reduced remuneration and also made full-time professors face the problems of layoffs and power transfer to administrative staff. More than that, in fact, corporatization also has an impact on the school itself, such as increasing construction costs and spending money to recruit more administrative staff. But I think that for schools, the pros and cons are about the same. They paid the price and got something, while students and professors didn’t benefit a lot from it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Works Cited&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Mills, Nicolaus. “The Corporatization of Higher Education.” Dissent (00123846), vol. 59, no. 4, Fall 2012, pp. 6–9. EBSCOhost, &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1353/dss.2012.0087&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1353/dss.2012.0087&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Lerner, Gerda. “Corporatizing Higher Education.” History Teacher, vol. 41, no. 2, Feb. 2008, pp. 219–27. EBSCOhost, &lt;a href=&quot;https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;amp;db=eric&amp;amp;AN=EJ791732&amp;amp;site=ehost-live&amp;amp;scope=site&quot;&gt;https://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;amp;db=eric&amp;amp;AN=EJ791732&amp;amp;site=ehost-live&amp;amp;scope=site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Bose, Purnima. “Faculty Activism and the Corporatization of the University.” American Quarterly, vol. 64, no. 4, Dec. 2012, pp. 815–18. EBSCOhost, &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1353/aq.2012.0058&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1353/aq.2012.0058&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Cadambi Daniel, Malini. “Contingent Faculty of the World Unite! Organizing to Resist the Corporatization of Higher Education.” New Labor Forum (Sage Publications Inc.), vol. 25, no. 1, Winter 2016, pp. 44–51. EBSCOhost, &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1177/1095796015620408&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1177/1095796015620408&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">Jiantao Li Dr. Tagnani ENGL 101 November 28, 2022 Research Argument: The impact of the corporatization of higher education is doing more harm than good</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Writing assignment # 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/10/20/paper-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Writing assignment # 2" /><published>2022-10-20T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-10-20T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/10/20/paper-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/10/20/paper-2.html">&lt;p&gt;Jiantao Li&lt;br /&gt;
Dr. Tagnani&lt;br /&gt;
ENGL 101&lt;br /&gt;
October 20, 2022&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Corporatization in Higher Education&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Chapter 10 of “The Coddling of the American Mind”, authors Greg Lukianoff and Jonathan Haidt mention the concept of university corporatization. As today’s universities become more diverse, more administrators and managers are hired and given more power. This trend is the corporatization of universities. Taking this as the theme, I will explain how the corporatization of the university is formed, and the influences and results of the corporatization of the university, based on the relevant materials I have found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;font color=&quot;red&quot;&gt;Firstly, the formation of university corporatization is caused by the increase in the number of students and tuition fees, so most schools choose to become more diversified to attract more students and thus earn more tuition fees. Combined with the data given in the article &quot;The Coddling of the American Mind&quot;, we can understand why universities choose corporatization. The article expresses&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;p&gt;in 1869, there were only 63,000 students in American institutions of higher learning and today, there are about 20 million students in higher education institutions. In other words, because there are more students, tuition is higher, and the university makes more money. So, universities want to attract more students and increase their revenue, and they turn themselves to diversification, for example in research, education, fundraising, branding, and legal compliance. With the advent of these programs, the university needs more staff to manage the relevant departments. Therefore, the formation and development of the administrative department gave birth to the prototype of corporatization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only that, as well as in the article “The corporatization of higher education”, author Rebecca Clay simply pointed out that the rise of consumerism and the continuous push for accountability has led to the corporatization of higher education. In this article, Harvard University President Derek Bok explains that the corporatization of higher education is nothing new, “What is new about today’s commercial practices is not their existence but their unprecedented size and scope.” (Universities in the Marketplace: The Commercialization of Higher Education, Princeton, 2004). Bok believes that the growing commercialism of society is a factor in the corporatization of high education but is not the only force at work. Cynthia Belar, Ph.D., APA’s executive director for education, believes that social accountability also contributes to the corporatization of higher education, saying “There’s a perception by the public that there has been waste in higher education and that there needs to be more accountability for the dollars spent.”(10).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus, it is not difficult to understand how the corporatization of higher education came into being. Diversity in universities, the prevalence of consumerism and commercialization, and the push for accountability have all contributed to this result.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly, among higher education institutions, the most affected by corporatization are part-time and full-time professors at community colleges. Adopting a business model in higher education is a particular challenge for community colleges, according to Juli A. Jones’ article “Foundations of Corporations: Lessons from the Community College.” Because community college students expect financial success and rapid progress through convenient programs, their administrators insist on increasing productivity at all costs by increasing class sizes and improving student retention, including lowering academic standards. Therefore, community college professors will become more frequently used due to the influence of corporatization, especially part-time professors, and become more passive and difficult due to the expectations of students and the lowering of academic standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, a 2006 report by the American Historical Association found that 68 percent of community college historians worked there as adjunct faculty. With low funding for community colleges, community colleges must rely on overwhelming part-time jobs, some of which are graduate students at local colleges. “Their poor pay requires many to take overloaded schedules with no job security, without basic support such as office space, pay for office hours, library or internet privileges, and of course without benefits.” (Jones 214) Part-time faculty at community colleges must bear a lot of work and risks, as well as meager wages because of the commercialization or corporatization of the college. And it’s just as bad for full-time professors in higher education institutions. 
Consequently, because of commercialization and corporatization, fewer full-time professors are employed, which means that full-time faculty within colleges must take on more workloads and courses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, the result of the corporatization of higher education is that universities see students as consumers. Because corporatization makes universities more profitable, they need to meet the needs of “consumers” as much as possible, so that more “consumers” can generate more profits for “companies.” In “Coddling”, The authors give strong data “From 2003 to 2013, public research universities increased spending on student services by 22.3%, which was far more than the increases for research (9.5%) or instruction (9.4%).” (189) These data show that Universities prefer to meet the needs of students and attract more students, rather than improve their education level. 
Meanwhile, the article “The corporatization of higher education” also quotes what a psychology professor said, “The concept of students as customers cannot possibly have a positive influence. Pandering to students rather than expecting them to do work to get a decent grade is not a very good idea, to put it mildly. “ (Buck 2) So, it doesn’t seem like a good idea to think of students as consumers. In addition, the author also gives his views on meeting the needs of students in the article “Foundations of Corporations: Lessons from the Community College.” The authors argue that remote and online classes meet the needs of students while allowing universities to do more with less. Efficiency can be increased using technology, with fewer teachers. 
However, this also has a negative result, “Of course, such a philosophy encourages students to see grades and degrees as commodities and to devalue the process of education, development of -analytical skills, and the traditional liberal arts.”(215)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, combining these three articles, it is not difficult to see that the corporatization of universities is caused by the rise of consumerism and the continuous accountability system. The most serious and important impact of corporatization is the full-time and part-time professors in community colleges. Because of corporatization, their treatment has been greatly affected. In the end, the result of corporatization is that universities see students as consumers, and it’s hard to define whether this is a good outcome, but these articles give their views.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;font color=&quot;red&quot;&gt;Modification:

I made some changes to the structure of the article&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Works Cited&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Jones, Juli A. “Foundations of Corporatization: Lessons from the Community College.”, vol. 41, no. 2, 2008, pp. 213–17. , &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jstor.org/stable/40543825&quot;&gt;http://www.jstor.org/stable/40543825&lt;/a&gt;. Accessed 19 Oct. 2022.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Clay, R. A. (2008, December 11). The corporatization of higher education., (11). &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apa.org/monitor/2008/12/higher-ed&quot;&gt;https://www.apa.org/monitor/2008/12/higher-ed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Haidt, Jonathan, and Greg Lukianoff. The Coddling of the American Mind. Penguin Books, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">Jiantao Li Dr. Tagnani ENGL 101 October 20, 2022 The Corporatization in Higher Education In Chapter 10 of “The Coddling of the American Mind”, authors Greg Lukianoff and Jonathan Haidt mention the concept of university corporatization. As today’s universities become more diverse, more administrators and managers are hired and given more power. This trend is the corporatization of universities. Taking this as the theme, I will explain how the corporatization of the university is formed, and the influences and results of the corporatization of the university, based on the relevant materials I have found. Firstly, the formation of university corporatization is caused by the increase in the number of students and tuition fees, so most schools choose to become more diversified to attract more students and thus earn more tuition fees. Combined with the data given in the article &quot;The Coddling of the American Mind&quot;, we can understand why universities choose corporatization. The article expresses in 1869, there were only 63,000 students in American institutions of higher learning and today, there are about 20 million students in higher education institutions. In other words, because there are more students, tuition is higher, and the university makes more money. So, universities want to attract more students and increase their revenue, and they turn themselves to diversification, for example in research, education, fundraising, branding, and legal compliance. With the advent of these programs, the university needs more staff to manage the relevant departments. Therefore, the formation and development of the administrative department gave birth to the prototype of corporatization. Not only that, as well as in the article “The corporatization of higher education”, author Rebecca Clay simply pointed out that the rise of consumerism and the continuous push for accountability has led to the corporatization of higher education. In this article, Harvard University President Derek Bok explains that the corporatization of higher education is nothing new, “What is new about today’s commercial practices is not their existence but their unprecedented size and scope.” (Universities in the Marketplace: The Commercialization of Higher Education, Princeton, 2004). Bok believes that the growing commercialism of society is a factor in the corporatization of high education but is not the only force at work. Cynthia Belar, Ph.D., APA’s executive director for education, believes that social accountability also contributes to the corporatization of higher education, saying “There’s a perception by the public that there has been waste in higher education and that there needs to be more accountability for the dollars spent.”(10). Thus, it is not difficult to understand how the corporatization of higher education came into being. Diversity in universities, the prevalence of consumerism and commercialization, and the push for accountability have all contributed to this result. Secondly, among higher education institutions, the most affected by corporatization are part-time and full-time professors at community colleges. Adopting a business model in higher education is a particular challenge for community colleges, according to Juli A. Jones’ article “Foundations of Corporations: Lessons from the Community College.” Because community college students expect financial success and rapid progress through convenient programs, their administrators insist on increasing productivity at all costs by increasing class sizes and improving student retention, including lowering academic standards. Therefore, community college professors will become more frequently used due to the influence of corporatization, especially part-time professors, and become more passive and difficult due to the expectations of students and the lowering of academic standards. Furthermore, a 2006 report by the American Historical Association found that 68 percent of community college historians worked there as adjunct faculty. With low funding for community colleges, community colleges must rely on overwhelming part-time jobs, some of which are graduate students at local colleges. “Their poor pay requires many to take overloaded schedules with no job security, without basic support such as office space, pay for office hours, library or internet privileges, and of course without benefits.” (Jones 214) Part-time faculty at community colleges must bear a lot of work and risks, as well as meager wages because of the commercialization or corporatization of the college. And it’s just as bad for full-time professors in higher education institutions. Consequently, because of commercialization and corporatization, fewer full-time professors are employed, which means that full-time faculty within colleges must take on more workloads and courses. Finally, the result of the corporatization of higher education is that universities see students as consumers. Because corporatization makes universities more profitable, they need to meet the needs of “consumers” as much as possible, so that more “consumers” can generate more profits for “companies.” In “Coddling”, The authors give strong data “From 2003 to 2013, public research universities increased spending on student services by 22.3%, which was far more than the increases for research (9.5%) or instruction (9.4%).” (189) These data show that Universities prefer to meet the needs of students and attract more students, rather than improve their education level. Meanwhile, the article “The corporatization of higher education” also quotes what a psychology professor said, “The concept of students as customers cannot possibly have a positive influence. Pandering to students rather than expecting them to do work to get a decent grade is not a very good idea, to put it mildly. “ (Buck 2) So, it doesn’t seem like a good idea to think of students as consumers. In addition, the author also gives his views on meeting the needs of students in the article “Foundations of Corporations: Lessons from the Community College.” The authors argue that remote and online classes meet the needs of students while allowing universities to do more with less. Efficiency can be increased using technology, with fewer teachers. However, this also has a negative result, “Of course, such a philosophy encourages students to see grades and degrees as commodities and to devalue the process of education, development of -analytical skills, and the traditional liberal arts.”(215) In conclusion, combining these three articles, it is not difficult to see that the corporatization of universities is caused by the rise of consumerism and the continuous accountability system. The most serious and important impact of corporatization is the full-time and part-time professors in community colleges. Because of corporatization, their treatment has been greatly affected. In the end, the result of corporatization is that universities see students as consumers, and it’s hard to define whether this is a good outcome, but these articles give their views. Modification: I made some changes to the structure of the article Works Cited</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Writing assignment # 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/09/26/paper-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Writing assignment # 1" /><published>2022-09-26T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/09/26/paper-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/09/26/paper-1.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/files/book.png&quot; alt=&quot;Book&quot; width=&quot;35%&quot; align=&quot;right&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;    &lt;font color=&quot;red&quot;&gt;In Chapter 2 of “The Coddling of The American Mind”, authors Greg Lukianoff and Jonathan Haidt make a point about Antifragility. In the article, Nassim Nicholas Taleb, professor of risk engineering at New York University, shared his views and perspectives on Antifragility. &amp;lt;1&amp;gt;&lt;/font&gt; In his 2007 best seller, “The Black Swan,” Taleb argues that calculating risk based on experience is the wrong way to think about risk. He pointed out that life is unpredictable, and no one knows when the next accident will happen. In his later book, Antifragility, he explained how systems and people, like the immune system, become stronger in response, able to survive the inevitable risks. And he also states that we need to distinguish between fragile, resilient, and antifragile, and he used china teacups and plastic cups as examples. Our anti-vulnerability systems become rigid and inefficient when we don’t have the stress and challenges we need to learn, adapt, and grow. This is the tragedy of modern times: like overprotective parents, those who try to help us often hurt us the most. &lt;font color=&quot;red&quot;&gt;Taleb uses a poetic example, &quot;You want to be the fire and wish for the wind.&quot;, to advise that the wind will extinguish the candle and ignite the fire. Do not turn a child into a candle. &amp;lt;2&amp;gt; Because accidents, risks, and stress are an inevitable part of life, growing and learning from these experiences is what children need most. &amp;lt;3&amp;gt;&lt;/font&gt; Nowadays, most parents do not prepare their children to face the risks and challenges. &lt;font color=&quot;red&quot;&gt;They try to clear all the difficulties along the way, not realizing that one day, the children will leave the umbrella of home. By the time children are faced with independent living, too little independent experience can leave them at a loss. &amp;lt;4&amp;gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;    I quite agree with the author’s points. &lt;font color=&quot;red&quot;&gt;Parents’ love for their children is understandable, but excessive involvement in children’s life, study, and friendship will affect children’s independent growth, and because parents are overprotective, children will feel inferior and afraid of challenges, resulting in their lack of experience. &amp;lt;5&amp;gt;&lt;/font&gt; In addition, there are many examples of overprotection in our lives, such as fear of unsanitary ground, always holding the child in my arms, not letting the child play, fear of soiling his clothes, forbidding the child to take off his shoes on the beach, fear of broken glass Injure their feet and teach children not to talk to strangers. Moreover, excessive protection of children is, in essence, excessive restrictions on children. Therefore, what should parents do? I have summarized some ways that I think are good to raise children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Let children make their own decisions and give them the chance to try and make mistakes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Put yourself in the child’s shoes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Let it go and give your child a free environment to grow up in.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Let children learn to protect themselves.
In China, there is a proverb, “Failure is the mother of success”. If a person has not experienced failure, he cannot succeed. If today’s kids have never experienced heavy rain, they won’t be able to see a rainbow either.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;font color=&quot;red&quot;&gt;Modification:

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    Make my sentence clearer.
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    Fixed citation errors.
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    Make my sentence clearer.
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    Make my sentence clearer.
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    Make my sentence clearer.
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/font&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Required Reading</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/08/31/book.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Required Reading" /><published>2022-08-31T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/08/31/book</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/08/31/book.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/files/book.png&quot; alt=&quot;The Coddling of The American Mind&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Course Calendar</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/08/31/calendar.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Course Calendar" /><published>2022-08-31T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/08/31/calendar</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/08/31/calendar.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/files/Calendar Fall 22.html&quot;&gt;See Course Calendar Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">See Course Calendar Here</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Syllabus</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/08/31/syllabus.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Syllabus" /><published>2022-08-31T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/08/31/syllabus</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2022/08/31/syllabus.html">&lt;iframe src=&quot;/files/Syllabus Fall 22.html&quot; width=&quot;750&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; frameborder=&quot;1&quot; name=&quot;iframe&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;   
&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>